German Democratic Republic Subject Files, Inclusive: 1951-2007, undated, Bulk: 1977-1990
Baylor University, The Keston Center for Religion, Politics, and Society
- Denominational, 1956-2004; 2
  - Evangelical Church. Relations with Other Believers, 1979-1990, undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Evangelical Church. Relations with Other Believers. Orthodox, 1974-1989, undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Evangelical Church. Ecumenical Relations, 1971-1990, undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Evangelical Church. Religion and National Identity (1 of 2), 1980-1984 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Evangelical Church. Religion and National Identity (2 of 2), 1985-1989, undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Evangelical Church. Pronouncements on Secular Affairs (1 of 2), 1965-1986 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Evangelical Church. Pronouncements on Secular Affairs (2 of 2), 1987-1990, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Evangelical Church. Christian Socialism (1 of 2), 1997-March 1998 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Evangelical Church. Christian Socialism (2 of 2), April 1998-1999, undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Evangelical Church. Peace (1 of 2), 1976-1982 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Evangelical Church. Peace (2 of 2), 1983-1987, undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Evangelical Church. Arts. Architecture. Language. Literature. Music, 1978-1987, undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Evangelical Church. Art, 1979-1985, undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Evangelical Church. Church Building Architecture and Restoration, 1977-1986, undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Evangelical Church. Literature, 1977-1990, undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Evangelical Church. Women, 1977-1989, undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Evangelical Church. Work with Children, 1977-1985, undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Evangelical Church. Children ( 1 of 2), 1977-1980 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Evangelical Church. Children ( 2 of 2), 1981-1998, undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Evangelical Church. Sociology and Family. Visual Material, 1980-1990, undated (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Evangelical Allianz. General, 1974-1990, undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Evangelical Lutheran Church. Martin Luther and the Lutheran Church (1 of 2), 1967-1987, undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Evangelical Lutheran Church. Martin Luther and the Lutheran Church (2 of 2), 1983 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Jehovah's Witness. General, 1983-1987, undated (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Judaism. General, 1971-2003, undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Judaism. Church. State. Law (1 of 2), 1971-1987 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Judaism. Church. State. Law (2 of 2), 1988-1989, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Mennonite Church. General, 1974-1990, undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Methodist Church. General, 1968-1989, undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Mormon Church. General, 1985-1988, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - New Apostolic Church. General, 1984-1988, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Orthodox Church. General, 1979-1990, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Pentecostal Church. General, 1975-1980, undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Quakers. General, 1965, undated (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Pietism (Pietisten). General, 1988, undated (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Reformed Church. General, 1984-1987, undated (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Roman Catholic. History. General, 1959-1990, undated (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Roman Catholic. History. Soviet Period, 1973-2001, undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Roman Catholic Church and State Relations, 1972-1990, undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Roman Catholic Church and State Legislations, 1980, undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Reopening of (Opening of New) Churches. Re-consecration, 1980-1989, undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Oppressive Practices. Attacks in the Media, 1973-1993, undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Festivals and Anniversaries, 1975-1989, undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Canonization and Beautification, 1979-1886, undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Services. Rituals. Liturgy, 1980, undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Pilgrimage and Saint Veneration, 1977-1989, undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Preaching. Evangelism. Conversion. Parish Life, 1978-1988, undated (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Defection from Faith, 1979-1983, undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Official Publications, 1977-1990, undated (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Monasticism, 1979-1988, undated (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Lay Workers Dairy, 1980-1989, undated (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Philanthropy, 1980-1988, undated (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Clergy and Priesthood, 1973-1990, undated (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Statistics, 1977-1990, undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Roman Catholic Church. International Relations. Hungary (1 of 2), 1956-1989 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Roman Catholic Church. International Relations. Hungary (2 of 2), 1990-1996, undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Delegation Visits Abroad, 1973-1990, undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Ecumenism, 1969-1990, undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Theology, 1971-1988, undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Relations with Fellow Believers, 1975-1990, undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Ecumenical Contacts with Other Denominations, 1977-1990, undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Involvement in Secular Affairs and Politics, 1974-1989, undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Arts. Architecture. Music. Literature, 1979-1989, undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Youth and Children, 1979-1987, undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Children, 1979-1990, undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Students, 1980-1981, undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Sociology and Family, 1975-1989, undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Salvation Army. General, 1984, undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - United Brethren Church. General, 1973-1986, undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Unierte Kirchen. General, 1980-1989, undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Free Churches (Frikirchen), 1980-1990, undated (Box 23, Folder 10)